(Sheldon:)Is this the Zack Johnson
(Sheldon:)who used to have coitus
with my neighbor Penny?
(Sheldon:)Sorry to bother you.
(Sheldon:)Hello. I'm looking
for a Zack Johnson
(Sheldon:)who used to have coitus
with my neighbor Penny.
(Sheldon:)Coitus. It means intercourse.
(Sheldon:)And I have a feeling I'm
speaking to the right Zack.
(Sheldon:)This is Sheldon Cooper.
(Sheldon:)Fine. Shelly.
(Sheldon:)Yes, that does
sound like a girl's name.
(Sheldon:)No, it doesn't bother me.
Yes, "Smelly Shelly"
does bother me.
(Sheldon:)Let me tell you why I'm calling.
(Sheldon:)I'd like to know
if you'd be interested
(Sheldon:)in having sex
with Amy Farrah Fowler.
(Sheldon:)Amy Farrah Fowler.
Yes, that is  a girl's name.
(Sheldon:)Good grief. It's like trying
to talk to a dolphin.
(Howard:)Really?